Look, it's me like this
I hid it so hard
It's so hard
Is this comfortable?
Grabbing me, I feel like
We're losing one by one
If you really want to turn the tables on girls, you can only rely on me
Hahaha, the ingredients are caught
Ap again sang a song
Sawadee ka
Who is the traitor?
The teacher said I'm the one who steals towers and deserves death
I'm not allowed to steal towers
Hahaha, can't bear it anymore, can't bear it anymore
I win everything
So what punishment did the brothers give us?
Go to the farm and catch that running chicken
The punishment we gave you is to reverse the chicken
Catch us
Starting from February 16th
Every Friday at 20:10
Broadcast on Hunan TV and Mango TV
Exclusive for members of the Members' Acceleration Battle
More exciting content in the Members' Loading Update
Ah, why is it me?
Come on, brothers
Hey
This gun is quite suitable for running today, feels good
Play, hahaha, play
Good luck is coming
Continue with the confession
Hey, how do I get in?
Never been in before
First time
How's the experience at home?
I didn't expect it to be so fast
I was originally
Then why was I caught?
Don't you press that something
Press that, load, load, load the photos, right?
Me and Xingge load together
And then, that hunter came from afar
And then
That hunter suddenly came over
Ah, after he came over, we ran
When we ran, it was me
So I thought I should crouch down
So I crouched down
No, I
I thought I might still be seen
I thought I would be fine if I looked up at him
I said you felt a bit inferior at that time
A bit inferior, a bit inferior
If you look into his eyes, it's fine
If you don't look at him, it's fine
You're quite inferior
You made eye contact, right?
Made eye contact, made eye contact
I'm bored staying here
When were you last caught?
I'm always
at the back
I don't want to stay here
I want to go out
Revive, revive me
I want to revive
Oh no
I think we're in danger in this round
To be honest
If you really want to turn the tide and make a comeback
You can only rely on me
Hmm, hahaha
What's wrong? What's wrong?
Is it true?
I mean, I can go to the scene to cheer you on
Treating me like this
If we revive, we'll be a couple
It's a must, we have to be together
You really have a small character
If we don't team up, it will be difficult to win
We can only say we must lose
Really, wow
Missing a gel
Hahaha
Adhesive, adhesive
Then what am I?
Hmm, you are a catalyst
Uh, a catalyst
Achieve twice the result with half the effort
But if it's just you alone
You, hahaha
So you shouldn't team up with others
This guy who fights with me gives everyone strength
What kind of strength?
I give you strength
Give me the strength to say something
And you embarrass yourself
They are now very dry, right? Very dry?
In pieces, in pieces
Take a look
Legend of the Dead Squad is caught
Caught
It's over
The odds are in our favor
Hahaha
Hey, this won't do
Hey, you're caught
Okay, okay, it's almost there, it's fine
Hahaha
Good, the difference is good
It's fine, it can be played
Hahaha
Ah, oh my god
Hey, it's not far, it's not far
So tired
If they lock it down
They really locked it down
Both of us must be together, right?
I have a question
If someone is caught
Then it's both of them, right?
Both of them
Shouldn't it be only one?
Only one
Then what about the handcuffs?
That's when it looks good
Both of them don't want to be caught by the hunter
The lover is only chasing
I thought you meant both feet
Both feet, that foot
Then before, the foot holds that one
No, the opponent leans towards the lover
Because the lover is only pursuing
That confidence
If we have to say who will die, it's someone else
Hahaha, no, no, no, hey
Ap, as long as you turn around, I'll push you
Hahaha, you're shameless
Too shameless
Oh, teammate revived
Come on, Xiao Zhou
Xiao Zhou, come on
I know, I know
Actually, Ap wants to reconcile with you
I understand, give me a hug
Come on, Xiao Zhou
Hahaha
Sit down, it's just me
I'm telling you, the way Jiuzhou netizens speak fits you perfectly
But you don't have it, mainly because
What if I do?
Wait for me
Jiuzhou
The waiter sent me a message
Asking why I got caught as soon as I came in
I got caught too
Hahaha, it's like forgetting to breathe
I resurrected once
Hahaha, I resurrected myself
And I resurrected myself
I want to say there's no sense of time
Yeah, I'll just go once
As long as it's just you who got eliminated
Then we have to sell drinks to others here
Is that so? Hahaha
We're going to sell
Sell agricultural products
I want to offer a hot drink to passersby
Tiger, hey
Xingge is here
Hahaha, the hunter
Hey, hunter, hunter
There's a hunter right behind the middle finger
Hunter, drink some water
Hahaha, shut up
I'm that panda
The experience is really bad
Hahaha, but it's not just the bad experience
I got caught on my first try
Actually
But you, even though the experience is bad
You completed the process instantly
Double life, yeah
Not bad, not bad
You see, this way you play, ah yeah
Game over, over
Overrun, I have the rebirth one
But I used it to save someone else, yes
I know, me, and I, I'm resurrected, how do you say it?
You were like two times
Double after, uh
Double life, double life
Double life, yeah
I rebooted one time
But you got caught too early, yeah, you run
Good morning in English
Study well, hahaha
I feel like I have a lot to say but can't say it
How did you get eliminated?
How? I'm not being wrong
Hahaha, uh, uh
Because I went to get number three
Number three, oh
I ran there
And then there were three ribbons
I remember tying them around my waist
And after that, the ribbons were right there, oh
Prince Hongfan was arrested
Uh, Prince
Prince Hongfan
Oh, with a Richard
Oh no, no
No, the hunter will catch
Prince, ah
Because
Aldrin, Aldrin, team win
Win!
Ouch!
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no
Can't even run straight anymore
Hurry, let's go
Let's welcome the prince
The prince has come to our Dongzi County
Welcome, welcome, welcome, welcome, welcome
Beware of the hunter
At this time, it's usually time to say "brother"
Well done, come back, yes
It's up to you, brothers
Come on, victory is ours
Sir and Ah Qizi
Ah Qizi, Ah Qizi's Mt picture picture
Hahaha, no residential area, no residential area
Going back to Changsha
There's a residential area, go back to Changsha and back to
Hahaha, hello, hello
Nice to meet me
Hahaha
Angel, live
Angel, don't mind
Angel is the best singer
It's so scary to watch
Really? World-class singer
Pay attention to the other one
Hahaha, but Xiaopu sang with him
His singing is very good
Let Enqi sing
Enqi sings
Enqi's singing is hilarious
Is that so?
I guess it's for the sake of the show
Not bad, this bride is for the show, right?
Really for the show?
Is that right?
Enqi sings beautifully
Come on, let's all sing a song
Do you trust my character?
When did I ever lie to you?
Brother, you have no conditions
It was Jin who took off his clothes
Why?
Because it's hot, hahaha
He just changed his shoes
Really? Maybe he's just like his uncle
He's going to take off the height insoles
You don't have height insoles
I'm already this tall, why would I have height insoles, bro?
Come on, give me your shoes
Shoe cover, shoe
Put on the shoe cover
Get up, get up
Who am I?
Hahaha
You're too weak
No height increaser, no height increaser
Wipe me, wipe me, wipe me, wipe me
Don't mind, don't mind, no problem
Wow hahaha
It's too high, wow
Why did you take them off?
To take them off like this
Look, the right foot is my shoe
Right, hahaha, too tall
The right foot is my shoe
What are you really doing?
Still trying to fool me
Not caring about height
Hahaha
I saw it a few days ago
You haven't arrived yet
Did you see that?
No.
Why did the ball you just hit fly away?
I ran straight at it.
And then you caught me right away.
When I was ten, I wanted to protect you.
But I accidentally ran too fast.
I disappeared.
I turned around again.
My snot and photography, none of them is there.
Which party is this?
This is another party.
Another party.
Leader, tell me seriously.
Your three seconds.
Did you have any thoughts of protecting me?
Yes, yes, yes.
Really? Do you really have?
I think you're lying.
What's your expression like?
Me, Zicui, and who else is here with you.
And bullying.
No.
What I mean is, what I mean is...
Brother, it's up to you.
Hey, brother.
Ah, Wuxi has been caught.
What do we do, what do we do?
What do we do?
What do we do, you've lost another general.
We have 5 left.
You have 3 left.
You should care about your team.
No, it's not like that.
Hahaha, it's like this.
You caught me.
It's like this, our team.
There's a skill called "the less blood, the stronger."
Is it really cool?
Exactly.
Hahaha, yes, yes, hit me.
You have a skill called Cement, do you know?
Water, diamond, mud.
It's okay, Xu De.
He's here.
He, he, he's here.
He asked me before.
It's not Xu De.
Hahaha, I'm afraid it's me.
Because I have a friend named Jersey.
Which friend?
Hahaha, telling lies.
Work's over, hard work.
Hard work, hard work.
Are you really newlyweds?
Or just acting?
Acting, we're really a couple.
You should treat him well, hahaha.
The immortal in the city was caught.
The resurrection object also went offline.
Wow, Alan Tree, Alan Tree.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
Wow, wow.
Wow, wow, wow.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
Wow, wow.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
Wow, wow, wow.
Wow, wow.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
Wow wow wow wow
Wow wow
Wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow
But I was actually hiding there
He's hiding there too
It's quite interesting
We're still passionate and energetic
Looks like he's relaxed
Look at the plateau
Hahaha
Dedede
Let me read an idiom
What's going on?
Why are you staring at me?
Hahaha Lirui Jie Maisu Bi
The game is great
My good teammate
I, I'll protect you while I'm resting
But you're in the next room now
We're still separated
It's okay, it's okay
We're connected in heart
They're focusing on us
Your hands have such complicated colors
There are more purple yams
I'm so torn
It's okay, it's okay
Beautiful purple orange
You're making me angry
Hahaha
Haha
Oh
Aunt, is there anything you want to say?
Look at what you've done to me on these broadcasts
Look at Jinge
I have a question for you
What is it?
Do you want me to die here or is it real?
Hahaha, it's not me
What have you done to me recently?
It's Ahu who got caught and dragged me down
Yeah, he got caught and it affected my offline status
Yes, it was when we were checking in
I just received a task
He called me and treated me
I saw that troupe over there
Where is it, Chen?
Over there, in the TV drama
I've been chasing that troupe
I rushed back in the end
I even captured the successful one
I've captured it
It's great, just missed the ship
And then they said time was up
And we were reported
And now I'm caught again
You gave me the wrong information
It made me waste time to complete my check-in
And now I'm caught because of him
Don't stop me
Don't worry about him
Don't hit him, Fatty
Fatty, stop hitting
Stop hitting
Officer, officer
All of this, all of this is our big brother's arrangement
The teacher said I'm a person deserving of death
Xiaoxian, look at all the information I have, it's all a strategy
Xin ge, did you see where he is?
(Note: Due to the length of the text, the translation may not match perfectly with the original subtitles. Please make sure to cross-reference the original and translated texts for accuracy.)
Yeah, take a look
Hahaha
Hey, sister, what are you doing again?
Instant change of expression
Just now, he totally blew me away
I'm special now
He, he, I don't have a teammate anymore
So, our final formation is a dead team
Living as a team
We're doomed, haha
Little Super Brother got caught
Wow
Wow, two
Two positions, wow
Wow
Good
The next mission is designed for you
If you're here
Our mission
The last mission of listening to music
Is yours, Wang Yuexin
Yuwengwen is so powerful
Wow, music attributes dominate
On our side, Cao Enqi
On our side, Qiao Enqi
Red Star Xu Kai
Xu Kai is really daring
Hahaha, he's strong
Xu Kai got caught
Oh, Xu Kai got caught
Oh
Xu Kai got caught
Don't stop
Which side are you on?
You're such a two-faced person
Because, like that Brubru going back and forth
I always stand on this side of the wall
Which side are you on?
Are you just going with whoever has more people in the end?
Hahaha
Whoever, I always win
Wow, no
Another song came out
Yeah yeah
Hahaha
What's our punishment?
What did you decide?
Oh wow
I remembered, I remembered
Is ours scary?
Ours is pretty scary too
You guys go first
Then we'll do rock-paper-scissors
Rock-paper-scissors
You said hahaha
Didn't someone say that?
Hey, your rock-paper-scissors is unreliable
It's just a preliminary
It's kind of dumb, hahaha
Hahaha, you brought me back
Hahaha, what a joke
The captain bullies me
No, no
I'll go and teach him a lesson, hahaha
We can't go any further
We can't go any further, hahaha
Hey, it's enough
Very cool, very cool
Cool
Cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool
Cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool
Cool, cool, cool
Cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool
Cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow
Cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow
Cow cow cow cow cow cow
Cow cow
Cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow
Cow cow cow cow
Cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow
Cow cow
Cow cow cow cow
Cow cow cow cow cow
Cow cow
Cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow
Cow cow cow cow cow cow cow
Cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow cow sheep
Legend legend
Hahaha us
Do you know how I guessed you would shoot?
I guessed you would shoot like this
Hahaha okay
Oh oh hahaha
Come on, come on
You, the person I meet anytime
Angie
Okay, as you wish
No problem with whatever you choose
Great
Hey hey, why is there one more person in the countdown?
5 4 3 2 1
Ahhh
Hahaha, everyone worked hard
Everyone worked hard
The team leader is great
Hahaha
Hey, your props are amazing
Listen to me, our props are amazing
But we also have your burden
Hahahaahaha
Ahhh
Ahh
Oh oh oh
Hey, I always believed that you could do it, amazing
That's enough, that's enough
Hey
So what punishment did the brothers give us?
Go to the farm and catch that running chicken
The punishment we set for you is
Reverse the machine
Catch us hahaha
Well, it's not impossible
Over here, over here
This is the cabin
Start the machine triumphantly
Ahhh
Put it back, put it back
Hey hey hey hey
Aren't you supposed to be amazed?
Why can each one of them fly?
Ahh hey, we caught the fruit back
Why did you catch the chicken?
Wow wow, okay okay okay okay
Today's highlight
Today's most shining heroes are on you
Hahaha
Wow, it feels like a band
How about we start with a song
Let's have a song
Hey, hey, isn't that full speed ahead
Full speed ahead
This speed is very effective
You see, if there are
people, you can go around at this speed
I think this way of dodging is good
I think if I dodge like this
Dodge like this
Dodge like this and come out
Dodge like this if they come straight
This is the best way to group
Not like that, group like this
In case they come around to this side
If you see the enemy coming over now
You go around like this
In his perception, he will turn this way
But before he turns, you go around to this side
Then you'll be safe
OK, hehe
I can do it like this
What characters are written here
I can't see when I'm writing now
Military Song Protecting the Body
Just four characters
So direct
Oh yeah, today
My goal
is to do my best to protect this country
and try my best to make it to the third round
The way to pass this round
Now let's pass the first round first
I'm now
I've already entered the second round today
Right?
Brother Sheng
It turns out that the chance of survival for me is higher
I will also go around
I run slowly
But I can go around
I think this angle is good
This angle is a new one I've studied
A good angle, huh
I can see him
They can't see me
There are some angles
I guess that sense of rhythm
Hey Lao Zhang, I'm waiting for him here
Let me wait for him for a while
Hmm, the hotline for disconnection is quite hot
Okay, okay
You don't move
I'll go activate number 5
I'm also next to number 5
Okay, okay
You go, but you need to calculate well
You may not go when I get there
Oh, I didn't expect to run over this time
Damn, I have over a hundred or two hundred steps in my heart
Why did he run so fast
Slow down, I beg you
Don't run
Don't move, let me rest for a while
When my steps reach 3, then
I have to press 3, I don't care
The thing is over there
Hey, you need to hide for a while.
You can hide next to these two characters.
Give him the flesh column, his lover.
Give him the flesh column.
I think this one is better.
This one is good.
I didn't expect it, didn't expect it.
The remaining Fruit King can also pass.
Really unexpected.
Hey, hey, hey.
Red flower 180180.
Hello, gentlemen.
Are you trying to show off?
Ah, this is it.
How do you look?
Why didn't you say hello to me?
I accidentally grew it.
We were rehearsing the other day.
You looked fine then.
What did you eat these days?
These days, I've had a bit too much oily food.
I'll hide here first.
Did you see 5th squad?
Two 5th squads.
I didn't see 5th squad.
I saw 6th squad.
I gathered my people.
It's this leg.
Let me tell you.
Make this leg a bit thicker for me.
Make it slightly thicker for me.
Then I can hide.
Captain Jiuzhou has been caught.
He got caught so quickly.
Only a few seconds have passed.
He must have solved the Hunter's Eye.
It's 9th squad.
It's already over.
What is my goal for this show?
The original goal was not to die first.
Now I have achieved my goal.
When will they find us?
I think I just ate that ice cream.
Okay.
Ah, it's so boring.
Let me increase my step count.
The pottery workshop is definitely a landmark.
I think the Maitreya Eye is also one.
Ah, I found it.
Smart.
Now it's my turn.
I'm nervous when I see someone in black.
He's right there, he's right there.
He's just right there.
Wow, so fast, so fast.
So scary.
I hope he can't fly.
This drink won't make it over.
This is getting dangerous.
If he comes down from above
It's a bit dangerous
This guardian is safe for me
This guardian is relatively safer
I feel pain
There shouldn't be a problem
They probably won't catch me
Last 5 minutes
Hold on, victory is ours
Game time is up
Orange team has 2 survivors
Purple team has 1 survivor
Red team wins this round
Finally, I can take off this piece of junk
It's so difficult
It's okay, I'm on vacation
Ah, feels good
Welcome to our home
Living room, hmm
It's a bit small though
It's too cold
Hmm
Is it comfortable like this?
This is above the abdomen gym
So this is Building 1, OK
What about Building 2?
Building 5, Building 6
Let's eat this first
Whoever is closer to the kaleidoscope is closer to Device 5
Go and take a look
Go to the exclusive hunter
Activate your brain
Come on
Let me check the 11th spot in Shandong
So only the top-ranked can pull
I'm about rank four
I'll take four first
After taking four, I'll try to take six
Liang Ge, Liang Ge
I found the merchant
He's with Allen
Now you see it, huh?
The center strategy is the most dangerous place
It's also the safest place
You must find a corner to hide
Because hunters only see in straight lines
Oh my god
The captain also went offline
Am I going to rely on myself next?
Since we're here now
We're just hiding, right?
Hmm, let me simulate the scene where the hunter comes
Wait, didn't you see me?
10-year membership card
Hahaha
Our 10-year membership card
Supports mobile phones, computers, iPads, TVs, projectors
What are you doing?
If you don't avoid a person, who are you chatting with?
Are you still here?
Look, look
Just dodge a bit, ah
I am sculpting, this is a sculpture.
Not this.
This is good, it has many twists and turns.
Welcome.
Thank you for your patronage.
Is it a secret code?
Or is it related to the clue?
Welcome.
Thank you for your patronage.
Thank you, Yilin.
I, I am deducing.
Because of the last one.
I feel like it's related to the agricultural union.
I have a hunter here.
Oh my god.
I'm jealous for a week.
Have this hunter sit next to me instead.
There was a hunter guarding you just now.
Did you know?
They really can't do without me.
Because I am indeed their brother.
Hahaha.
Call Brother Luohu.
Hey, Kai Kai.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm just strolling.
It's okay, it's okay.
Check if there's a hunter near you.
I don't have a hunter here.
But when you come, it's like having a hunter.
So you don't welcome me.
It's not that we don't welcome you.
It's just...
Brother really loves you.
But in this show, it's better for you not to come.
Hahaha, just tell him.
Be generous and let him come.
Tell him to go to the Longken Museum.
This museum...
Okay, okay, it's okay.
I won't come.
I won't come, I'll see where you are.
If they activate the exclusive people to catch Xie Yuling,
Then we will win two points.
No, the brothers won't be so heartless.
Teacher Xie Yuling is also a senior.
The brothers won't be so heartless.
Prince Hongfan is caught.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
Hahaha, it's not because Prince was caught.
At least one of us,
If Sister Luming is caught,
Then we will be two people short.
I knew it.
The brothers will definitely protect us more in this situation.
This is a rare opportunity.
Right, right, hey.
Why are you sitting here all the time?
I'm just conserving energy by sitting here.
Like you, right?
I have to keep you here.
Oh, I'm just ready for a swap.
No, I'm going to find Su Xing.
No, I'm going to find Xie Yilin.
You're smart.
Just now, I went to find Xie Yilin.
So quickly, one for one.
What one for one?
0 to 2
Ah, looks like you can't escape
When the hunter comes later, I'll jump into the water
Can't outrun on land
Can't escape in the water either
Hahaha, you're thinking the same as me
Why am I wearing this?
Do you know?
No, our team
We can't afford to lose anyone
Even if I die today
I will chase till victory
Divide, divide, divide, divide, divide, divide, divide, divide
But now I have learned
That is, in the future, if there's any trouble
It's really just like this
We must find the Flame Emperor first
Learn till old, learn till old
There's a feeling of surviving on a deserted island
After experiencing being caught for the first time
That fearless feeling is gone
But being able to stay alive is the most important thing
But being able to survive is the most important thing
Actually, my current strategy and plan is
To go to as many task points as possible
And see if we can complete some tasks
See if there's anything that can help us
To win in the future
Currently, I'm ranked 11th in steps
Which means
I must quickly increase my steps
And try to rank 6th
It's hard for me to move forward at this speed
Because everyone is shaking their phones
Or running fast
I kicked, I kicked, I kicked
Take a round, take a round
Short by 200 steps, short by 100 steps
Ah, got pulled again
Oh my god
Brother, you're so handsome
I really love you
Let's take a picture together
Oh, I just took a photo
Did my verification fail just now?
Welcome, Captain Xiaoqi
I can also call you Xiaoqi
Really? I can also call myself Cao Weisi
Why can't I call myself Xiaoqi?
I am Xiaoqi
What did you say?
Hey, girl
We need to take a picture together
Xiaoqi, we need to take a picture
I, I, we have
I'm lucky to take a picture with Brother Xiaoqi
Then let's take a picture together
Let's take a picture together
Okay, let's take it
That's great, I thought I was Xiaoqi
Because you found another Xiaoqi
Due to Huang Zihongfan's arrest
Xie Enlin chose to pair with
Su Xing as the resurrection target
And entered the paired Xie
If Xie Lin is arrested
Then Su Xing can switch to another resurrection target
If Su Xing is arrested, he can change the resurrection target
That means
For example, if there's another mission next time
Could it be possible that I
For example, let the hunter capture the councilor
In that case
Then there will be a loss of two people as a pair
For the team, it will gain numerical advantage
Thank you, hello, hi
Hello, I am Xiao Anqi from this team
Hello, thank you
Just now, you helped us
Should we go out for a walk together?
I'll help you
The sun is perfect
It's the time to enjoy the sun
Just a little bit, do you want me to carry bricks?
Be honest in life
It's okay, I'm next to Yi Jie
Have you made a deal with Jing Ge?
Quickly say that you haven't reached an agreement with Xu Ke
If you haven't made a deal with Xu Ke
Then I will, I will, I will kick you out
I really
You haven't made a deal with Xu Ke, right?
No, then I'll let the hunter come find me
Ying Jie, I really like you
I like your show, keep it up
Take a silly photo with Xiao Qi Ge
If you are my fan
You will definitely sing along
Definitely sing along
If you don't sing, you're definitely not a fan
Hey, still here
Still here
We invite him to sing another song, how about it?
Give this former fan a chance
The chair
I don't need the chair anymore
Xiao 7 said squatting is good for me
I like, I like
Doing this squat jump
Okay
I think this VIP spot suits you well
Girls' concerns
That one is black
I'll just take this
Let me show you
In a blink of an eye, sacrifices are made
It's over, it's over
It's dangerous on this road